export const test = {
  englishTest: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: 'What is a synonym for Hi?',
      answers: ['Hello', 'Bye', 'Hibye', 'YesNo'],
      correctAnswer: 'Hello',
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: 'What is a synonym for late?',
      answers: ['sale', 'not on time', 'Thesaurus', 'sample'],
      correctAnswer: 'not on time',
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: 'What is a synonym for Question?',
      answers: ['beautiful', 'quiz', 'Day', 'Word'],
      correctAnswer: 'quiz',
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: 'Whats meaning of Student?',
      answers: [
        'Table',
        'Teacher',
        'Female',
        'who is studying for their first degree at a college or university.',
      ],
      correctAnswer:
        'who is studying for their first degree at a college or university.',
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: 'What is a synonym for Bye?',
      answers: ['Hello', 'Night', 'Hibye', 'see you'],
      correctAnswer: 'see you',
    },
  ],
  mathTest: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: 'Whats the average of 3, 8, 2523?',
      answers: ['844.666', '846.666', '744.666', '884.666'],
      correctAnswer: '844.666',
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: 'Whats it? 2 + 2',
      answers: ['5', '11', '22', 'two + two'],
      correctAnswer: 'two + two',
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: 'Whats sin(78.78)?',
      answers: ['98 * 10 ^ -4', '0.098', '0.98088', '2!'],
      correctAnswer: '0.98088',
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: 'Whats sqrt(8998)?',
      answers: ['94.85', '79.22', '92.25', 'No answer!'],
      correctAnswer: '94.85',
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: 'Whats 2 * 3',
      answers: ['8', '12', '6', '66'],
      correctAnswer: '6',
    },
  ],
};
